

## **About Me**

Innovative Web Developer with experience in design web pages.

Strong written and oral communication skills resulting in knowledgeable, satisfied customers. Excellent instructional and problem solving skills reduce concerns related to new technology.



+963994608051



yahea.loulou@gmail.com



Damascus, syria

### LANGUAGE

- arabic(native)
- English(excellent)

## **TECHNICAL PROFILE**

- HTML
- CSS(bootstrap)
- JavaScript
- react
- Next is
- Python
- 🦫 C++
- 🦻 c#
- sql
- redux
- wordpress

# YAHYA LOULOU

programmer

### **EXPERIENCE**

please click here to show my portfolio

https://yahyaloulou.vercel.app/

react front-end web developer Mad solutions - syria 2024



about 3 months of training in react web developing build projects and deploy it .

backend odoo developer noptechs - Turkey 2022 - 2023

implementation systems and customize odoo tools to suit the client using python .

IT support specialist. house of colors - Syria 2021 - 2022

IT supporting for the web application that used in mobile application for house of colors problem solving and big experience in printers systems.

sales manger Golden mobile - syria 2019- 2021

selling mobile phones and accessories for clients and for golden mobile vendors.

### **EDUCATION**

BA in information technology engineering

2019-Currennt syrian virtual university

building website using wordpress

2023

mamdouh kaldas ,edrak platform

front end developer certificate

2022

meta, coursera platform

CEH V11

2022

with hani alsayes coatch.